<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Distributed Camp 2020</title>
    <link>https://distributed.camp/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Distributed Camp 2020</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 16:56:16 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://distributed.camp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Our first official logo!</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/2020/05/21/our-first-official-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 18:06:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/2020/05/21/our-first-official-logo/</guid>
      <description>As we mentioned in &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s up with that logo?&amp;quot;, one of the community values is that &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rsquo;re all participants&amp;rdquo;.
We held a Design Jam pre-event for our registered participants and came up with a really solid first logo!
  We are so very pleased with all of the participation from campers and project leads, but an extra special shout-out is due to @ricky. Be sure to give them a cheer on our Discord server!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I2P - The Invisible Internet Project</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/projects/i2p/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 16:56:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/projects/i2p/</guid>
      <description>What is I2P? You can find out more by visiting their site https://geti2p.net</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beaker Browser</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/projects/beaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 16:56:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/projects/beaker/</guid>
      <description>What is Beaker? You can find out more by visiting their site https://beakerbrowser.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPFS - The Interplanetary File System</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/projects/ipfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 16:56:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/projects/ipfs/</guid>
      <description>What is IPFS? You can find out more by visiting their site https://ipfs.io/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebTorrent</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/projects/webtorrent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 16:56:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/projects/webtorrent/</guid>
      <description>What is Webtorrent? You can find out more by visiting their site https://webtorrent.io/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Distributed Camp</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/about-distributed-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 18:10:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/about-distributed-camp/</guid>
      <description>If you wish to know more about the event, see Welcome to Distributed Camp
Distributed Camp is a unique event produced by Bimo Studio
It is a passion project of Bimo Studio to grow participation in technologies which are shaping the future of the Internet and to facilitate creators of all types.
The mechanics of how this event came to exist will be covered in one of the Sunday talks in the hopes that you (yes YOU) will grow the subsequent generations of camps for topics which are important to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 18:10:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Distributed Camp General Code of Conduct &amp;amp; Confidentiality Agreement
Ignorance is not an acceptable excuse for conduct that results in harassment. Scope The Distributed Camp Code of Conduct applies to all members, event attendees, partners, sponsors, exhibitors, media, and representatives of Distributed Camp paid or unpaid (referred to hereafter as “representatives”), in any context in which a reasonable observer might deem the individual to be acting as an agent or representative of Distributed Camp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 18:10:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/contact/</guid>
      <description>Report a Code of Conduct violation Please contact our team we&amp;rsquo;re here to help. Our Code of Conduct is available here
Bizdev / Sponsorships Would you like to boost Distributed Camp? Contact our Bizdev team.
Discord Distributed Camp Discord Server</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 18:10:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Friday, May 29:  AM Slot :  Start - 9AM Central (2PM UTC) - I2P  End - 1PM Central (6PM UTC) - Hard stop for AM Slot  PM Slot :  Start - 2PM Central (7PM UTC) - IPFS  End - 6PM Central (11PM UTC) - Hard stop for PM Slot  Saturday, May 30:  AM Slot :  Start - 9AM Central (2PM UTC) - DAT / Beaker Browser End - 1PM Central (6PM UTC) - Hard stop for AM Slot  PM Slot :  Start - 2PM Central (7PM UTC) - WebTorrent  End - 6PM Central (11PM UTC) - Hard stop for PM Slot  Sunday, May 31: - AM Slot :  Start - 9AM Central (2PM UTC) - Unconference &amp;amp; Participant Showcase 12:30PM Central (5:30PM UTC) - Closing remarks and call for feedback End - 1PM Central (6PM UTC) - Hard stop  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome To Distributed Camp</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/2020/03/29/welcome-to-distributed-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 18:06:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/2020/03/29/welcome-to-distributed-camp/</guid>
      <description>Distributed Camp is a unique event meant to highlight technologies which are changing the future of the Internet to empower users with new means of creating, hosting, and distributing content.
The Goal We wish for this to be an accessible, safe, and fun experience for all participants.
As much as is possible, we want participants to be able to engage in hands-on activities so they can achieve a firm grasp of the current capabilities of each featured project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s up with that logo?</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/2020/03/29/whats-up-with-that-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 18:06:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/2020/03/29/whats-up-with-that-logo/</guid>
      <description>One of the community values is that &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rsquo;re all participants&amp;rdquo;.
The initial design of the logo is to imply autonomy with the opportunity for connection. Admittedly though, there is a lot of room for growth.
As one of our first pre-events, we&amp;rsquo;re opening up the design of the logo to you.
Most of you should be able to spot the first easy fix (don&amp;rsquo;t mix stylized fonts), but where will you take it from there?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/readme/</guid>
      <description>Cupper 
An accessibility-friendly Hugo theme, ported from the original Cupper project.
Table of contents  Demo Minimum Hugo version Installation Updating Run example site Configuration Logo Favicons Shortcodes Syntax highlighting Disable toc for a blog post Getting help Credits  Demo https://cupper-hugo-theme.netlify.com/
Minimum Hugo version Hugo version 0.60.1 or higher is required. View the Hugo releases and download the binary for your OS.
Installation From the root of your site:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>