<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>untagged on Distributed Camp 2020</title>
    <link>https://distributed.camp/tags/untagged/</link>
    <description>Recent content in untagged on Distributed Camp 2020</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 18:10:29 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://distributed.camp/tags/untagged/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Distributed Camp</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/about-distributed-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 18:10:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/about-distributed-camp/</guid>
      <description>If you wish to know more about the event, see Welcome to Distributed Camp
Distributed Camp is a unique event produced by Bimo Studio
It is a passion project of Bimo Studio to grow participation in technologies which are shaping the future of the Internet and to facilitate creators of all types.
The mechanics of how this event came to exist will be covered in one of the Sunday talks in the hopes that you (yes YOU) will grow the subsequent generations of camps for topics which are important to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 18:10:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Distributed Camp General Code of Conduct &amp;amp; Confidentiality Agreement
Ignorance is not an acceptable excuse for conduct that results in harassment. Scope The Distributed Camp Code of Conduct applies to all members, event attendees, partners, sponsors, exhibitors, media, and representatives of Distributed Camp paid or unpaid (referred to hereafter as “representatives”), in any context in which a reasonable observer might deem the individual to be acting as an agent or representative of Distributed Camp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 18:10:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/contact/</guid>
      <description>Report a Code of Conduct violation Please contact our team we&amp;rsquo;re here to help. Our Code of Conduct is available here
Bizdev / Sponsorships Would you like to boost Distributed Camp? Contact our Bizdev team.
Discord Distributed Camp Discord Server</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 18:10:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Friday, May 29:  AM Slot :  Start - 9AM Central ( UTC) - I2P  End - 1PM Central ( UTC) - Hard stop for AM Slot  PM Slot :  Start - 2PM Central ( UTC) - IPFS  End - 6PM Central ( UTC) - Hard stop for PM Slot  Saturday, May 30:  AM Slot :  Start - 9AM Central ( UTC) - DAT / Beaker Browser End - 1PM Central ( UTC) - Hard stop for AM Slot  PM Slot :  Start - 2PM Central ( UTC) - WebTorrent  End - 6PM Central ( UTC) - Hard stop for PM Slot  Sunday, May 31: - AM Slot :  Start - 9AM Central ( UTC) - Unconference &amp;amp; Participant Showcase 12:30PM Central ( UTC) - Closing remarks and call for feedback - - End - 1PM - Hard stop  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>