<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Distributed Camp 2020</title>
    <link>https://distributed.camp/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Distributed Camp 2020</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 18:06:18 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://distributed.camp/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Our first official logo!</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/2020/05/21/our-first-official-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 18:06:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/2020/05/21/our-first-official-logo/</guid>
      <description>As we mentioned in &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s up with that logo?&amp;quot;, one of the community values is that &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rsquo;re all participants&amp;rdquo;.
We held a Design Jam pre-event for our registered participants and came up with a really solid first logo!
  We are so very pleased with all of the participation from campers and project leads, but an extra special shout-out is due to @ricky. Be sure to give them a cheer on our Discord server!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome To Distributed Camp</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/2020/03/29/welcome-to-distributed-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 18:06:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/2020/03/29/welcome-to-distributed-camp/</guid>
      <description>Distributed Camp is a unique event meant to highlight technologies which are changing the future of the Internet to empower users with new means of creating, hosting, and distributing content.
The Goal We wish for this to be an accessible, safe, and fun experience for all participants.
As much as is possible, we want participants to be able to engage in hands-on activities so they can achieve a firm grasp of the current capabilities of each featured project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s up with that logo?</title>
      <link>https://distributed.camp/2020/03/29/whats-up-with-that-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 18:06:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distributed.camp/2020/03/29/whats-up-with-that-logo/</guid>
      <description>One of the community values is that &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rsquo;re all participants&amp;rdquo;.
The initial design of the logo is to imply autonomy with the opportunity for connection. Admittedly though, there is a lot of room for growth.
As one of our first pre-events, we&amp;rsquo;re opening up the design of the logo to you.
Most of you should be able to spot the first easy fix (don&amp;rsquo;t mix stylized fonts), but where will you take it from there?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>